[
  {
    "Question": "parque",
    "Answer": "park"
  },
  {
    "Question": "hospital",
    "Answer": "hospital"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iglesia",
    "Answer": "Church"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Cine",
    "Answer": "cinema"
  },
  {
    "Question": "biblioteca",
    "Answer": "library"
  },
  {
    "Question": "librería",
    "Answer": "bookstore"
  },
  {
    "Question": "teatro",
    "Answer": "theater"
  },
  {
    "Question": "hotel",
    "Answer": "hotel"
  },
  {
    "Question": "museo",
    "Answer": "museum"
  },
  {
    "Question": "correo",
    "Answer": "post office"
  },
  {
    "Question": "banco",
    "Answer": "bank"
  },
  {
    "Question": "panadería",
    "Answer": "bakery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "farmacia",
    "Answer": "pharmacy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "carnicería",
    "Answer": "butcher shop"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapatería",
    "Answer": "shoestore"
  },
  {
    "Question": "salón de belleza",
    "Answer": "beauty salon"
  },
  {
    "Question": "supermercado",
    "Answer": "supermarket"
  },
  {
    "Question": "peluquería",
    "Answer": "barbershop"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zoológico",
    "Answer": "zoo"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tienda",
    "Answer": "store"
  },
  {
    "Question": "estación de bomberos",
    "Answer": "fire station"
  },
  {
    "Question": "aeropuerto",
    "Answer": "airport"
  },
  {
    "Question": "parada de autobuses",
    "Answer": "bus stop"
  },
  {
    "Question": "estación del tren",
    "Answer": "train station"
  },
  {
    "Question": "bodega",
    "Answer": "warehouse"
  },
  {
    "Question": "almacén",
    "Answer": "department store"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mercado",
    "Answer": "market"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gasolinera",
    "Answer": "gas station"
  },
  {
    "Question": "centro comercial",
    "Answer": "mall"
  },
  {
    "Question": "piscina",
    "Answer": "pool"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gimnasio",
    "Answer": "gym"
  },
  {
    "Question": "garaje",
    "Answer": "garage"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mueblería",
    "Answer": "furniture store"
  },
  {
    "Question": "heladería",
    "Answer": "ice cream parlor"
  },
  {
    "Question": "vecinos",
    "Answer": "neighbors"
  },
  {
    "Question": "casa",
    "Answer": "house"
  },
  {
    "Question": "barrio",
    "Answer": "neighborhood"
  },
  {
    "Question": "calle",
    "Answer": "street"
  },
  {
    "Question": "avenida",
    "Answer": "avenue"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cuadra",
    "Answer": "block"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mi dirección",
    "Answer": "my address"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ciudad",
    "Answer": "city"
  },
  {
    "Question": "campo",
    "Answer": "country"
  },
  {
    "Question": "bosque",
    "Answer": "forest"
  },
  {
    "Question": "selva",
    "Answer": "jungle"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Las montañas",
    "Answer": "mountains"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Universidad",
    "Answer": "university/college"
  },
  {
    "Question": "colegio",
    "Answer": "high school"
  },
  {
    "Question": "escuela",
    "Answer": "school"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cárcel",
    "Answer": "jail"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Quién",
    "Answer": "Who"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Qué",
    "Answer": "What"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Cuándo",
    "Answer": "When"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Dónde",
    "Answer": "Where"
  },
  {
    "Question": "De dónde",
    "Answer": "From where"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Adónde",
    "Answer": "To where"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Por qué",
    "Answer": "Why"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Cómo",
    "Answer": "How"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Cuál",
    "Answer": "Which"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Cuánto",
    "Answer": "How much"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Cuántos",
    "Answer": "How many"
  },
  {
    "Question": "los días de semana",
    "Answer": "the days of the week"
  },
  {
    "Question": "hoy",
    "Answer": "today"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mañana",
    "Answer": "tomorrow"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lunes",
    "Answer": "Monday"
  },
  {
    "Question": "martes",
    "Answer": "Tuesday"
  },
  {
    "Question": "miércoles",
    "Answer": "Wednesday"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jueves",
    "Answer": "Thursday"
  },
  {
    "Question": "viernes",
    "Answer": "Friday"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sábado",
    "Answer": "Saturday"
  },
  {
    "Question": "domingo",
    "Answer": "Sunday"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el mes",
    "Answer": "the month"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el año",
    "Answer": "the year"
  },
  {
    "Question": "enero",
    "Answer": "January"
  },
  {
    "Question": "febrero",
    "Answer": "February"
  },
  {
    "Question": "marzo",
    "Answer": "March"
  },
  {
    "Question": "abril",
    "Answer": "April"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mayo",
    "Answer": "May"
  },
  {
    "Question": "junio",
    "Answer": "June"
  },
  {
    "Question": "julio",
    "Answer": "July"
  },
  {
    "Question": "agosto",
    "Answer": "August"
  },
  {
    "Question": "septiembre",
    "Answer": "September"
  },
  {
    "Question": "octubre",
    "Answer": "October"
  },
  {
    "Question": "noviembre",
    "Answer": "November"
  },
  {
    "Question": "diciembre",
    "Answer": "December"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Padres",
    "Answer": "parents"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Madre",
    "Answer": "mother"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Padre",
    "Answer": "father"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Esposo",
    "Answer": "husband"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Esposa",
    "Answer": "wife"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Marido",
    "Answer": "husband"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Marida",
    "Answer": "wife"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hijo",
    "Answer": "child/son"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hija",
    "Answer": "daughter"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Niño",
    "Answer": "child"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hermanos",
    "Answer": "siblings"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hermano",
    "Answer": "brother"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hermana",
    "Answer": "sister"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tío",
    "Answer": "uncle"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tía",
    "Answer": "aunt"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Sobrino",
    "Answer": "nephew"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Sobrina",
    "Answer": "neice"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Abuelo",
    "Answer": "Grandpa"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Abuela",
    "Answer": "Grandma"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Abuelos",
    "Answer": "grandparents"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Nietos",
    "Answer": "grandchildren"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Nieto",
    "Answer": "grandson"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Nieta",
    "Answer": "granddaughter"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Primos",
    "Answer": "cousins"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Primo",
    "Answer": "cousin"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Prima",
    "Answer": "cousin"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Bisabuela",
    "Answer": "Greatgrandmother"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Bisabuelo",
    "Answer": "Greatgrandfather"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Bisabuelos",
    "Answer": "Greatgrandparents"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Madrastra",
    "Answer": "stepmother"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Padrastro",
    "Answer": "stepfather"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hermanastro",
    "Answer": "stepbrother"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hermanastra",
    "Answer": "stepsister"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Padrino",
    "Answer": "Godfather"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Madrina",
    "Answer": "Godmother"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Me llamo Juan.",
    "Answer": "My name is John."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Soy de Nueva York.",
    "Answer": "I am from New York."
  },
  {
    "Question": "¿Cómo te llamas?",
    "Answer": "What is your name?"
  },
  {
    "Question": "¿De dónde eres?",
    "Answer": "Where are you from?"
  },
  {
    "Question": "¿Cuántos años tienes?",
    "Answer": "How old are you?"
  },
  {
    "Question": "¿Cómo se llama?",
    "Answer": "What is his/her name?"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Se llama Juanita.",
    "Answer": "Her name is Janie."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Este es mi amigo Juan.",
    "Answer": "This is my friend John."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Esta es mi amiga Juanita.",
    "Answer": "This is my friend Janie."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Soy Paco.",
    "Answer": "I am Paco."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Yo también.",
    "Answer": "Me too."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Su nombre es María.",
    "Answer": "Her name is Maria."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mi nombre es Julieta.",
    "Answer": "My name is Juliet."
  },
  {
    "Question": "¿De dónde es él?",
    "Answer": "Where is he from?"
  },
  {
    "Question": "¿De dónde es ella?",
    "Answer": "Where is she from?"
  },
  {
    "Question": "¿Cómo se llama usted señor?",
    "Answer": "What is your name sir?"
  },
  {
    "Question": "¿Qué te gusta?",
    "Answer": "What do you like?"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Me gusta la pizza.",
    "Answer": "I like pizza."
  },
  {
    "Question": "No me gusta el taco.",
    "Answer": "I don't like the taco."
  },
  {
    "Question": "¿Te gusta el taco?",
    "Answer": "Do you like the taco?"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Los apuntes",
    "Answer": "notes"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La clase",
    "Answer": "class"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La aula",
    "Answer": "classroom"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el director",
    "Answer": "principal"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el pupitre",
    "Answer": "student desk"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el escritorio",
    "Answer": "teacher desk"
  },
  {
    "Question": "la silla",
    "Answer": "chair"
  },
  {
    "Question": "la hoja de papel",
    "Answer": "sheet of paper"
  },
  {
    "Question": "la carpeta",
    "Answer": "folder"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el libro",
    "Answer": "book"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el cuaderno",
    "Answer": "notebook"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el cuaderno de ejercicios",
    "Answer": "workbook"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el diccionario",
    "Answer": "dictionary"
  },
  {
    "Question": "la pluma",
    "Answer": "pen"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el bolígrafo",
    "Answer": "pen"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el lápiz",
    "Answer": "pencil"
  },
  {
    "Question": "la goma",
    "Answer": "rubber eraser"
  },
  {
    "Question": "la goma de borrar",
    "Answer": "rubber eraser"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el borrador",
    "Answer": "eraser"
  },
  {
    "Question": "la tiza",
    "Answer": "chalk"
  },
  {
    "Question": "la pizarra",
    "Answer": "chalkboard"
  },
  {
    "Question": "la mochila",
    "Answer": "backpack"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el armario",
    "Answer": "locker"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el estante",
    "Answer": "bookshelf"
  },
  {
    "Question": "un pase",
    "Answer": "a pass"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el cesto de papeles",
    "Answer": "waste paper basket"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el basurero",
    "Answer": "trash bin"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el reloj",
    "Answer": "clock"
  },
  {
    "Question": "la cinta",
    "Answer": "tape"
  },
  {
    "Question": "la regla",
    "Answer": "ruler"
  },
  {
    "Question": "las tijeras",
    "Answer": "scissors"
  },
  {
    "Question": "las sacapuntas",
    "Answer": "pencil sharpener"
  },
  {
    "Question": "la grapadora",
    "Answer": "stapler"
  },
  {
    "Question": "la grapa",
    "Answer": "staple"
  },
  {
    "Question": "la tarea",
    "Answer": "homework"
  },
  {
    "Question": "la bandera",
    "Answer": "flag"
  },
  {
    "Question": "los carteles",
    "Answer": "posters"
  },
  {
    "Question": "las ocupaciones",
    "Answer": "the occupations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "el trabajo",
    "Answer": "the job"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trabajar",
    "Answer": "to work"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ganar dinero",
    "Answer": "to earn money"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ganar la vida",
    "Answer": "to earn a living"
  },
  {
    "Question": "camarero/mesero",
    "Answer": "waiter"
  },
  {
    "Question": "camarera/mesera",
    "Answer": "waitress"
  },
  {
    "Question": "doctor/medico",
    "Answer": "doctor"
  },
  {
    "Question": "piloto",
    "Answer": "pilot"
  },
  {
    "Question": "abogado",
    "Answer": "lawyer"
  },
  {
    "Question": "bombero",
    "Answer": "firefighter"
  },
  {
    "Question": "músico",
    "Answer": "musician"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cartero",
    "Answer": "mailman"
  },
  {
    "Question": "plomero",
    "Answer": "plumber"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jardinero",
    "Answer": "gardener"
  },
  {
    "Question": "panadero",
    "Answer": "baker"
  },
  {
    "Question": "banquero",
    "Answer": "banker"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cocinero",
    "Answer": "chef/cook"
  },
  {
    "Question": "peluquero",
    "Answer": "barber"
  },
  {
    "Question": "veterinario",
    "Answer": "veterinarian"
  },
  {
    "Question": "bibliotecario",
    "Answer": "librarian"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lechero",
    "Answer": "milkman"
  },
  {
    "Question": "secretaria",
    "Answer": "secretary"
  },
  {
    "Question": "es muy trabajador(a)",
    "Answer": "is a very hard worker"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mecánico",
    "Answer": "mechanic"
  },
  {
    "Question": "carpintero",
    "Answer": "carpenter"
  },
  {
    "Question": "atleta/deportista",
    "Answer": "athlete/athletic"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dama de la casa",
    "Answer": "housewife"
  },
  {
    "Question": "enfermera",
    "Answer": "nurse"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chófer",
    "Answer": "driver"
  },
  {
    "Question": "carnicero",
    "Answer": "butcher"
  },
  {
    "Question": "soldado",
    "Answer": "soldier"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cajero",
    "Answer": "cashier"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Obrero",
    "Answer": "worker/laborer"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Partes del cuerpo",
    "Answer": "Parts of the body"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La cabeza",
    "Answer": "the head"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El cuello",
    "Answer": "The neck"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Los hombros",
    "Answer": "The Shoulders"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El pecho",
    "Answer": "The chest"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La espalda",
    "Answer": "The back"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El estomago",
    "Answer": "The stomach"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El corazón",
    "Answer": "The heart"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Los brazos",
    "Answer": "The arms"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Las manos",
    "Answer": "The hands"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Los dedos",
    "Answer": "Fingers / toes"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Las uñas",
    "Answer": "The finger/toenails"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Las piernas",
    "Answer": "The legs"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Las rodillas",
    "Answer": "the knees"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Los codos",
    "Answer": "The elbows"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Los pies",
    "Answer": "The feet"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El tobillo",
    "Answer": "The ankle"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La muñeca",
    "Answer": "The wrist"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La cara",
    "Answer": "The face"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La frente",
    "Answer": "The forehead"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Las orejas",
    "Answer": "The ears"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El pelo/cabello",
    "Answer": "The hair"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La nariz",
    "Answer": "The nose"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Los ojos",
    "Answer": "The eyes"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Los labios",
    "Answer": "The lips"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La mejilla",
    "Answer": "The cheek"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Los dientes",
    "Answer": "The teeth"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La lengua",
    "Answer": "The tongue"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La boca",
    "Answer": "The mouth"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Las pestañas",
    "Answer": "The eyelashes"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Las cejas",
    "Answer": "The eyebrows"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Los días de la semana",
    "Answer": "The days of the week"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lunes",
    "Answer": "Monday"
  },
  {
    "Question": "martes",
    "Answer": "Tuesday"
  },
  {
    "Question": "miércoles",
    "Answer": "Wednesday"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jueves",
    "Answer": "Thursday"
  },
  {
    "Question": "viernes",
    "Answer": "Friday"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sábado",
    "Answer": "Saturday"
  },
  {
    "Question": "domingo",
    "Answer": "Sunday"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Los meses del año",
    "Answer": "The months of the year"
  },
  {
    "Question": "enero",
    "Answer": "January"
  },
  {
    "Question": "febrero",
    "Answer": "February"
  },
  {
    "Question": "marzo",
    "Answer": "March"
  },
  {
    "Question": "abril",
    "Answer": "April"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mayo",
    "Answer": "May"
  },
  {
    "Question": "junio",
    "Answer": "June"
  },
  {
    "Question": "julio",
    "Answer": "July"
  },
  {
    "Question": "agosto",
    "Answer": "August"
  },
  {
    "Question": "septiembre",
    "Answer": "September"
  },
  {
    "Question": "octubre",
    "Answer": "October"
  },
  {
    "Question": "noviembre",
    "Answer": "November"
  },
  {
    "Question": "diciembre",
    "Answer": "December"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ayer fue...",
    "Answer": "Yesterday was..."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Today is...",
    "Answer": "Hoy es..."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tomorrow is...",
    "Answer": "Mañana es..."
  },
  {
    "Question": "¿Cuál es la fecha de hoy?",
    "Answer": "What is the date today?"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La fecha es...",
    "Answer": "The date is..."
  },
  {
    "Question": "El cinco de mayo",
    "Answer": "The 5th of May"
  },
  {
    "Question": "August 22nd",
    "Answer": "El veintidós de agosto"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hoy es el veintidós de agosto",
    "Answer": "Today is the 22nd of August"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hoy es el primero de enero",
    "Answer": "Today is the first of January"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The weekend",
    "Answer": "El fin de semana"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El cuarto",
    "Answer": "The room"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El dormitorio",
    "Answer": "bedroom"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La cama",
    "Answer": "The bed"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El lavabo",
    "Answer": "The bathroom sink"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El fregadero",
    "Answer": "The kitchen sink"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La sala",
    "Answer": "The living room"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El baño",
    "Answer": "The bathroom"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La ducha",
    "Answer": "The shower"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La mesa",
    "Answer": "The table"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La silla",
    "Answer": "The chair"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La sofá",
    "Answer": "The sofa"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El garaje",
    "Answer": "The garage"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La ventana",
    "Answer": "The window"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La puerta",
    "Answer": "The door"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El armario",
    "Answer": "The closet"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La lavadora",
    "Answer": "The washing machine"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La secadora",
    "Answer": "The dryer"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El refrigerador / La refrigeradora",
    "Answer": "The refrigerator"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El horno",
    "Answer": "The oven"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La estufa",
    "Answer": "The stove"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El comedor",
    "Answer": "The dining room"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El jardín",
    "Answer": "The garden"
  },
  {
    "Question": "La mansion",
    "Answer": "the mansion"
  },
  {
    "Question": "El apartamento",
    "Answer": "apartment"
  }
]